<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>attack.t1552 on My New Hugo Site</title><link>https://bradleyjkemp.dev/sigmadoc/tags/attack.t1552/</link><description>Recent content in attack.t1552 on My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 23:58:33 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://bradleyjkemp.dev/sigmadoc/tags/attack.t1552/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Azure Kubernetes Admission Controller</title><link>https://bradleyjkemp.dev/sigmadoc/rules/cloud/azure/azure_kubernetes_admission_controller.yml/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 23:58:33 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bradleyjkemp.dev/sigmadoc/rules/cloud/azure/azure_kubernetes_admission_controller.yml/</guid><description>&lt;p>Identifies when an admission controller is executed in Azure Kubernetes. A Kubernetes Admission controller intercepts, and possibly modifies, requests to the Kubernetes API server. The behavior of this admission controller is determined by an admission webhook (MutatingAdmissionWebhook or ValidatingAdmissionWebhook) that the user deploys in the cluster. An adversary can use such webhooks as the MutatingAdmissionWebhook for obtaining persistence in the cluster. For example, attackers can intercept and modify the pod creation operations in the cluster and add their malicious container to every created pod. An adversary can use the webhook ValidatingAdmissionWebhook, which could be used to obtain access credentials. An adversary could use the webhook to intercept the requests to the API server, record secrets, and other sensitive information.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Google Cloud Kubernetes Admission Controller</title><link>https://bradleyjkemp.dev/sigmadoc/rules/cloud/gcp/gcp_kubernetes_admission_controller.yml/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 23:53:57 -0600</pubDate><guid>https://bradleyjkemp.dev/sigmadoc/rules/cloud/gcp/gcp_kubernetes_admission_controller.yml/</guid><description>&lt;p>Identifies when an admission controller is executed in GCP Kubernetes. A Kubernetes Admission controller intercepts, and possibly modifies, requests to the Kubernetes API server. The behavior of this admission controller is determined by an admission webhook (MutatingAdmissionWebhook or ValidatingAdmissionWebhook) that the user deploys in the cluster. An adversary can use such webhooks as the MutatingAdmissionWebhook for obtaining persistence in the cluster. For example, attackers can intercept and modify the pod creation operations in the cluster and add their malicious container to every created pod. An adversary can use the webhook ValidatingAdmissionWebhook, which could be used to obtain access credentials. An adversary could use the webhook to intercept the requests to the API server, record secrets, and other sensitive information.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Azure Keyvault Secrets Modified or Deleted</title><link>https://bradleyjkemp.dev/sigmadoc/rules/cloud/azure/azure_keyvault_secrets_modified_or_deleted.yml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 23:54:57 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://bradleyjkemp.dev/sigmadoc/rules/cloud/azure/azure_keyvault_secrets_modified_or_deleted.yml/</guid><description>&lt;p>Identifies when secrets are modified or deleted in Azure.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Azure Keyvault Key Modified or Deleted</title><link>https://bradleyjkemp.dev/sigmadoc/rules/cloud/azure/azure_keyvault_key_modified_or_deleted.yml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 23:50:56 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://bradleyjkemp.dev/sigmadoc/rules/cloud/azure/azure_keyvault_key_modified_or_deleted.yml/</guid><description>&lt;p>Identifies when a Keyvault Key is modified or deleted in Azure.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Azure Key Vault Modified or Deleted.</title><link>https://bradleyjkemp.dev/sigmadoc/rules/cloud/azure/azure_keyvault_modified_or_deleted.yml/</link><pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2021 23:41:43 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://bradleyjkemp.dev/sigmadoc/rules/cloud/azure/azure_keyvault_modified_or_deleted.yml/</guid><description>&lt;p>Identifies when a key vault is modified or deleted.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>